

Sirvan Doukchi

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Career Summary

Full stack developer, with hands-on IT experience, passionate motivated to actualise ideas all the way to implementing in browsers in a userfriendly and modern interface. I am resourceful, and committed to continually advancing my knowledge of relevant technologies including JavaScript, React JS/Native, HTML and CSS, Ruby on Rails, Node.JS and more.

Contact



Sydney, NSW



0406 471 ***



SirvanSh@gmail.com



www.Sirvan.Dev



@sirvan-doukchi



https://github.com/SirvanD

Skills

Languages

- JavaScript
- · Node.js
- Ruby
- CSS/SCSS

Database/Cloud

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- AWS

Techs

- Docker
- · Jira Workflow
- Github Actions
- Adobe Photoshop
- MS Azure
- CISCO CCNA

Frameworks/Libraries

- · React.js
- NextJS
- Sinatra/PG
- Bootstrap 5
- · Material UI

Software Engineering Projects

Servo App



- **JavaScript**
- Node JS / Express
- Google Maps Api
- **Government provided DB**
- **PostgreSQL**
- **Bootstrap 5**
- Deployed to Heroku

Space Watch www



- Node JS
- **User Authentication**
- OMDBI API
- CRUD actions
- Deployed to Heroku

BookShelf



- React
- **NodeJS / Express**
- MongoDB for Database
- **Firebase Authentication**
- Material UI
- · Google Books API and **REST API**

Tic Tac Toe www



- JavaScript
- DOM manipulation
- Vanilla JavaScript
- · CSS / Bootstrap

Work Experience

Clayton UTZ Law Firm

IT Support Analyst

Dec 2020- Sep 2021

Active directory administration, Microsoft Azure user groups, forest and domain management, shared drives, and application of SCCM, RDP, Logmein, and Skype remote consoles for assisting remote clients.

Melbourne Institue of Technology Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

IT Support Officer

Liaise with internal staff and students over the phone and on-site utilising HEAT ticket management for level 1 and 2 services and escalation of level 3 and security concerns to infrastructure teams.

Education

Software Engineering Immersive

General Assembly

Oct 2021 - March 2022

- · Creating full-stack applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Express with Node.js, and Version Control (Git and GitHub)
- Integrated third-party APIs into websites and applications
- · Working via remote correspondence and learning new methods of research, communication and collaboration

Masters in Information and Communication Technology

University of Wollongong

Jul 2016 - July 2018

• Post graduated with a distinction average with key subjects: Project and Change Management, Systems Integration, Information Systems and strategy, Strategic network design, IT security and Risk Management.